Privacy Policy

PM AM Corporation and its subsidiaries hereinafter referred as ‘PM AM’ is committed to respect your privacy and choices while using our website.  

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**  
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address, mailing address, phone number or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**  
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to a newsletter, fill out a form, Open a Support Ticket or enter information on our site.  
  
Provide us with feedback on our products or services 

**How do we use your information?**  
We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:  
      **•** To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.  
      **•** To improve our website in order to better serve you.  
      **•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.  
      **•** To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
      **•** To quickly process your transactions.  
      **•** To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products  
      **•** To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

**Personal Information Management:**  
Depending on local law, you may access, update, or correct your Personal Information that we hold, including your profile and preferences. If you have difficulty in updating or accessing your Personal Information as stated above, you may contact us at [admin@PMAM.com](mailto:admin@PMAM.com)

**Security**  
PM AM adopts reasonable and appropriate security practices and procedures that includes administrative, physical security, and technical controls in order to safeguard your Personal Information.

**Data Storage**  
PM AM may retain your Personal Information as long as there is a business requirement, or if otherwise required under applicable laws.

**Do we use 'cookies'?  
**Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.  
  
**We use cookies to:**  
      **•** Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.  
      **•** Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.  
  
You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser's Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  
  
**If users disable cookies in their browser:**  
If you turn cookies off, some features will be disabled. Some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and may not function properly.  
However, you will still be able to place orders access to the application, access to the site.  
  
**Third-party disclosure  
**We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your Personally Identifiable Information unless we provide users with advance notice. This does not include website hosting partners and other parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or serving our users, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release information when its release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others' rights, property or safety.   
  
However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third-party links  
**Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**Associate websites**  
PM AM may provide links to third-party websites and services. However, PM AM is not responsible for the privacy statements, practices, or the contents of such third-party websites.

**Contact us**  
If you may have any questions regarding this privacy statement, you may contact us using the information below.

**PM AM CORPORATION**  
5430 lyndon B Johnson Fwy #370,  
Dallas, TX 75240,  
United States  
  
Phone: 972 831 7400  
Fax: 972 831 7499  
E-mail: sales@pmam.com

**Updates to this privacy statement**  
PM AM may change the data privacy practices and update this privacy statement as and when the need arises, and the same will be made available on the website.

972-831-7400

Sales@pmam.com

5430 Lyndon B Johnson Fwy #370, Dallas, TX 75240, United States

© 2021. All rights reserved.

#### Request a Demo

×
